(Howard:)I'm sorry, Ma,
I have to stay late at the office.
No, he doesn't. He's lying to you.
(Howard:)Will you be quiet?
(Raj:)Well, if you want privacy,
let go of the ring.
(Raj:)I'm so glad we came
to this gentile strip club.
(Raj:)Howard, here's more bacon
to tuck into the shiksa's G-string.
[LAUGHS]
(Howard:)I'll call you back.
(Raj:)It's lovely you call your mommy
and let her know you're going to be late.
From what I know, if a woman
doesn't breast-feed on time...
(Raj:)...it's very uncomfortable for her boobies.
(Howard:)Don't you talk
about my mother's boobies.
(Raj:)If you're offended, let go of the ring
and go on home to your mother's boobies.
[RAJESH CHUCKLING]
(Sheldon:)Excellent. Tire each other out.
The ring will be mine.
(Sheldon:)Howard, why don't you
go after Raj's mother?
(Raj:)Why don't we go after your mother?
(Raj:)Go ahead.
I have no illusions about my mother.
(Sheldon:)She is a kind, loving,
religiously fanatical right-wing Texan...